KELSEY TOBIN

303-919-9637 | kelseytobindev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/kelseytobin | github.com/kelseytobin | www.kelseytobin.com

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer with experience in MERN stack and a passion for learning and creative expression. With a background in GIS and customer service, I transitioned to web development after experiencing technology's indisputable ability to solve problems. I feel the strong desire to contribute to an innovative, problem-solving community while working to brainstorm creative solutions to current processes, build relationships, and deliver results.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, PHP, HTML, CSS, WordPress, Shopify, React, Node, Mobile Design, MySQL, Mongo, Agile Workflow, Git, Heroku

PROJECTS

DateNite | github.com/kelseytobin/dateNite | dry-fortress-87482.herokuapp.com

- A web application providing date night idea suggestions and search tools
- Responsible for configuring user authentication and authorization using Passport.js and Bcrypt Worked with Google Places API to create routing and update html based on user search criteria
- Node.js Express.js MongoDB JavaScript ReactJS Passport.js Bcrypt MVC Pattern

The Berm | github.com/kelseytobin/The-Berm | fathomless-bastion-60475.herokuapp.com

- A mountain bike gear outlet designed specifically for female riders in a male dominated sport
- Built a RESTful API using Sequelize and an MVC pattern. Designed semantic view templates
- Node.js Express.js MySQL JavaScript Handlebars.js MVC Pattern

Get Out and Explore | github.com/Joshspeakman/Project-1 | joshspeakman.github.io/Project-1

- Event finding application that allows users to connect to a community anywhere around the world by dynamically updating the content of the web page with events occurring in the desired search location.
- Powered JavaScript and jQuery for AJAX functionality, custom front end CSS
- JavaScript jQuery Moment.js HTML CSS

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer - Jackson, WY 2019 - Present **Gliffen Designs**

Responsible for assisting with custom Wordpress site builds, re-builds, website security and maintenance, and database maintenance using Wordpress PHP JavaScript HTML CSS and MySQL. After being hired as an intern I was taken on by the team as a full time member.

Concierge - Teton Village, WY 2017-2019

Noble House Hotels and Resorts

I held the responsibility of billing and invoicing guest accounts, managing schedule coordination between guests of the lodge, contracted vendors, and upper management of the property while maintaining positive relationships with all of our vendors and partners.

Customer Service Representative - Teton Village, WY 2014-2016

Jackson Hole Mountain Resort

Worked to deliver a superior customer service experience for the guests of Jackson Hole Mountain Resort.

GIS Technician I - Fort Collins, CO 2014 CACI Inc

As a GIS technician I was responsible for creating maps for our contracted partners. I worked to facilitate the practical application of geographic spatial information by interpreting and managing digital land data.

EDUCATION

University of Denver, Full Stack BootCamp Certificate, Online Program University of Colorado, Boulder CO

Bachelors of Science - Geography